autnews.us 2017-06-16

# News| Politics | Logbook Loans | Same Day & Instant Cash Loans

### The Iran Crisis

* * *

There is an increasing sense of urgency among the israeli leadership over Iran's nuclear program and the possibility of taking military action to stop it.

The window in which to solve the crisis, as estimated by Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu at the UN last September as this spring or summer, is closing, and the prospect of a military strike looms.

It is Mr Netanyahu's opinion that further negotiations are fruitless and serve only to buy Iran more time.

* * *

"This programme lasted 38 minutes and 33 seconds, of which 31 minutes and 17 seconds consisted of talk time, including 123 appearances from 21 sources (including the narrator). Israeli sources, of which there were 15, appeared 55 times for a total of 15 minutes and 58 seconds - 51% of talk time, 41.4% of the programme, 71.4% of sources and 45% of source appearances."

"In stark contrast, the Iranian sources, of which there were just two, appeared three times for a total of 52 seconds - 2.8% of talk time, 2.2% of the programme, 9.5% of sources and 2.4% of source appearances. The first Iranian source does not appear until around 27 minutes into the documentary."

* * *

### Personal Finance

#### Logbook loans to be banned in the UK

"A [form of secured borrowing](http://www.kennethshamu.com/) known as logbook loans, or bill of sale lending, may be outlawed under government proposals. The department for business innovation and skills (BIS) is consulting on plans to ban what it calls the "archaic" and expensive method of borrowing. More than 1,000 people have [complained to the Office of Fair Trading](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/cash-loans-to-your-door.html) about these loans in the past four years. The loans are usually secured against the value of cars and allow the lender to repossess without a court order." Source: BBC News UK

#### Payday borrowers 'could complain' about lenders

"A host of small payday loan customers have [grounds for complaint](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/small-payday-loans.html) against lenders over the way repayments were collected, a charity has said. Citizens Advice said it saw 665 cases, of which 76% could have been forwarded to the Financial Ombudsman Service. These included cases of individuals being chased for a loan they had not taken out, it said. A string of payday lenders have signed up to a code of conduct aimed at improving standards. View payday loans online on [the Many-site](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/payday-loans-online.html)."

##### 'Pestered with texts'

Citizens Advice analysed a series of payday loan [cases](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/pounds-till-payday.html), which were reported to its customer helpline in the first half of the year. It found potential cases of fraud, such as being chased for non-existent loans. Others were "pestered" with phone calls and text messages, despite offers of repayments plans from customers. [Articles](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/instant-cash-loans.html) on instant cash loans can be found on www.diamondchoices.co.uk/instant-cash-loans.html. Some in financial difficulty were treated unfairly, according to the charity, and so could have taken a complaint to the ombudsman." Source: BBC News UK"

There are however some reputable firms that do exist. But even then, APRs still remain rather high when compared to mainstream credit. Diamond Choice for more information by [clicking the link](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/same-day-loans.html) or using their web address, www.diamondchoices.co.uk/same-day-loans.html.

### Payday Loan Alternatives

Related article: [The many company](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/payday-loans-for-unemployed.html). These types of loans have been at the receiving end of much bad publicity. Ministers and Church leaders have publicly stated their positions against these finance companie and yet even more people funded their christmas with payday loans despite [warnings](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/payday-loans-for-people-on-benefits.html) regarding payday loans for people on benefits. Now more and more communities are setting up credit unions to combat firms offering loans at high APRs such as those shown on http://www.boxpaydayloans.com/compare-payday-loans.html. These schemes are designed to drive expensive forms of credit out of the community, with payday lenders and doorstep lenders in their sights.

Recent news has highlighted the problem of payday brokers posing as payday lenders, although this is nothing new, as shown here http://www.boxpaydayloans.com/payday-loans-direct-lenders.html.

This warning comes from the Citizens Advice Bureau themselves stating that some consumers are being duped by brokers before being charged unexpected fees. These have been reported to be as high as £70 with brokers not making their role clear. This has left many believing they could get a loan, even without an income as demonstrated on http://www.boxpaydayloans.com/payday-loans-for-unemployed.html. 490 calls regarding complaints about brokers have been received by the service between June and July. Get [more information](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/quick-fast-payday-loans.html) on Manyloans.co.uk. This is the same site that is sometimes redirected to www.boxpaydayloans.com.

* * *

Having studied payday loans direct lenders only [blogs](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/payday-loans-direct-lenders-only.html), it has now become apparent how payday loans for people on benefits can have a negative impact on your dream to own your own home. According to a piece by the BBC, taking out a payday loan could endanger your chances of getting a mortgage regardless of whether you had difficulty repaying the loan or not. 66% of brokers contacted by _Mortgage Strategy_ , a trade publication, indicated that they had hda a client turned down for a mortgage application because of a guaranteed payday loans [application](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/guaranteed-payday-loans.html). Now there are plans to warn potential borrowers of the [danger/impact](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/instant-payday-loans.html) of using payday loans. A loan taken out will remain on your credit record for a period of up to 6 years. Some Mortgage applications are instantly declined and credit scores impacted negatively following a payday loan. It has been reported that this is the case even for High Street lenders.

These revelations make these loans even less attractive despite the [convenience](http://www.manyloans.co.uk/payday-loans-no-brokers.html) of payday loans no brokers. It is also speculated that the market will take a hit, seeing its value fall by up to 50%.

## Home Improvement Loans

Also of particular alarm is the high interest rates charged by some financial firms for [home improvement](https://www.honestjohn.ninja/) loans. This is an issue that has gone hand in hand with the controversial way in which double glazing windows are currently being sold.

* * *

#### PRIVACY POLICY for www.autnews.us

At www.autnews.us we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors. This Website Privacy Policy has been provided by the legal resource www.diylegals.co.uk and reviewed and approved by their solicitors. This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly. Information We Collect

In running and maintaining our website we may collect and process the following data about you

  1. Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  2. Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase.
  3. Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

##### Use of Cookies

Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website. We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer's hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. It is statistical data. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer. Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control. Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

##### Use of Information

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services.
  2. To provide information to you relating to other products that may be of interest to you. Such additional information will only be provided where you have consented to receiving such information.
  3. To inform you of any changes to our website, services or goods and products.

If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in. Where your consent has been provided in advance we may allow selected third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may interest you. Where such consent has been provided it can be withdrawn by you at any time.

##### Storing Your Personal Data

In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing. By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is treated stored securely. Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically. Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

##### Disclosing Your Information

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  1. In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
  2. Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
  3. To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.

##### Third Party Links

On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site's policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

##### Access to Information

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that we reserve the right to charge a fee of £10 to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information.

#### CONTACTING US

Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at support@autnews.us. No Autnews contact number is available.

* * *
